A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Welcome to Death Weapon Meister Academy.
More commonly known as the DWMA, it stands as a defense against the forces of evil, which
would plunge the world into chaos and drag humanity to the very depths of fear and madness.
The demons known as Kishan and their insatiable hunger for destruction.
To ensure the Kishan never regain their hold on this world, this academy was founded by
the Grim Reaper, Death himself.
So basically, we're an organization that exists to protect and preserve peace.
I guess it's not exactly a typical school.
Oh well, that isn't important.
For now, let's roll up our sleeves and get to work!
THE END
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
6人目も合わさず
運命まで絡んでく
行き先もらったポテル
食えない夜の端で
不可愛しすぎて
不可愛しすぎた眩しさが
悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が
胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
やっと理由は途絶びに引き付けられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
余す菜や
fake
I hundreds
そう
最高に
つもり
メンバー
トマス
I am the star.
The big man is showing up here?
Any trash who opposes me must be eliminated.
I mean immediately, you know.
Subaki, the head of the table, he's the target?
Yes, we're after Al Capone along with his associates.
About a hundred souls in all.
A hundred versus me, what I like.
Black Star.
Those are Kishan souls down there,
ones who have strayed out onto the path of evil.
We have to reclaim them all.
Assassin's rule number one, silence.
Dissolve in the darkness and erase your breath.
Wait for an opening to attack your target.
Assassin's rule number two, transpositional thinking.
Analyze the target in order to predict
his thoughts and movements.
Assassin's rule number three, speed.
Take out the target before the target
notices your presence.
Let's go.
I am the great assassin Black Star.
And I come here to assassinate you all.
Yahoo.
Hmm.
I am the great assassin Black Star.
And I come here to assassinate you all.
Yahoo.
Okay, that's all for now.
Excuse me.
okay that's all for now a weapon you don't understand assassination do you who are you
were those two ninjas don al capone yeah what is it you've been able to locate the witch
once we get this witch's power the family will become invincible you knew it
we had an awesome stage today sometimes i'm such a big star i almost can't handle it
great stage or not we still haven't collected a single soul that's become a kishin egg
you're acting more like a falling star using astronomy wordplay to insult me you shouldn't
use such a little joke on a big guy of course sorry about that however because i'm the bigger
man here i won't hold one poor joke against you i'll merely take it as a sign of your innocence
do you know how i'll respond to any more of these little jokes of yours subaki
by making a big joke of my own you laugh so much you'll be the falling star that wasn't a big joke
get it because you laugh so hard you'll fall down
oh yes i can barely stand up
any more of this and i won't have the dignity left to face lord death
i wonder if there are any good missions for us up there
what are you talking about we already have one we still have to take down capone and his thugs
we're on a bit of a losing streak right now black star maybe we should think about taking on an easier
mission yo looks like you two screwed up again last night huh i don't know what you're talking about
it was awesome i was the biggest star in the whole room yesterday i'm sure it was a great show black star
but shouldn't you be worrying about collecting some quiche and souls
yeah i guess i forgot that
what about you two how have you been doing lately
please don't ask
yeah it's too depressing to even think about right now
meister black star and tsubaki of class crescent moon please report immediately to the death room
i repeat
us what for
yeah yeah hello hello you two
i heard that you failed in the assassination of don al capone last night
we're very sorry
don't worry boss i've got it under control
i'm gonna turn tsubaki into a death scythe any day now i'm sure of it
until then why don't you take this copy of my autograph
like it even better than a death scythe huh
again i'm very sorry the problem with you two isn't skill you've got that but you don't seem to be
able to take the mission seriously enough
yes i had intended to observe your work over a longer period of time without interfering
but it seems that we have a problem on our hands
a problem al capone has targeted a witch and he and his henchmen have already mobilized
what the witch that they've set their sights on is named angela and she seems to have a very
powerful guardian protecting her if capone is able to defeat him and obtain the power of which
angela's soul things could get ugly wait a sec so if i beat al capone and the witch both let's see
your 99 kishin souls plus one witch soul i can make tsubaki a death scythe right there just
like that well that settles it come on let's hurry up and get going wait black star there's also
something that two of you should know about the witch angela oh hey they never listen
wait for me black star what is it we can't even succeed on a regular mission we'll never be able to
win against a win against a witch why not just trust me on this anyway we can't just rush into
this like we normally do we need to come up with a plan jeez subaki could probably partner up with
anyone she wanted to so why him black star's kind of an idiot but he's got guts he's not as much of a
jerk as he seems i'm sure subaki knows that by now yeah that may be why they work well anyway we
should get going too we still have 99 kishin souls to collect and a witch to defeat that's a long way
to go yeah there's a witch living inside this castle boss and after we capture her soul
my family will be the strongest you know don al capone
so al capone what could possibly bring a dirty mob boss like yourself to this castle
and if i don't like your answer you die well what do you know a tough guy kill him
we can't even succeed on a regular mission we'll never be able to win against a witch stupid subaki
how could she say that i don't care if it is a witch we're after it's a walk in the park taking
someone's soul is almost too easy for me i'll sneak up on subaki and show her how big of an assassin i am
assassins rule number one silence dissolve in the darkness and erase your breath wait for an opening
to attack your target
Silence means approaching quietly.
If you're trying to be an assassin, you have to learn how to shut up.
Oh, did I do that?
I'm dying now.
My breath will be erased.
Okay?
Okay!
Yahoo!
Where are you, witch?
It's time to die!
Hold on a second, Blackstar.
Did you come up with a plan for defeating Witch Angela?
Of course I did!
And it begins with me making a big entrance!
Well, I get it.
Obviously, you did not come up with a plan for us.
Don't worry, Subaki.
Okay?
I'm totally gonna turn you into a Death Scythe and a strong one.
Hold me on that.
I know you will.
I wonder what happened here.
This day is turning out to be a bit annoying.
These eggs.
There must be a hundred Gishin souls floating around here.
Are you responsible for all of this?
Did you come here hoping to collect the Witch Angela's soul?
Are you incredibly strong?
I hope you are.
Because I'm going to beat you in a bigger way than you could imagine!
Better get ready, cause we're gonna duel!
My name is Miflo.
I'm going to beat you in a bigger way than you could imagine!
Better get ready, cause we're gonna duel!
My name is Mifune.
I am the guardian of the Witch Angela.
My name is Blackstar.
I'll surpass the power of the Gods.
Did you come here hoping to collect the witch Angela's soul are you incredibly strong I hope you are because I'm going to beat you in a bigger way than you could imagine
Better get ready because we're going to duel
My name is Mifune I am the guardian of the witch Angela
My name is Blackstar I'll surpass the power of the gods
I prefer to kill only when necessary so leave this place and stay away from Angela
Subaki, right
So then you're a weapon Meister
Compared to a man as big as me you realize how small you are don't you
I understand how you feel
Even I can be frightened by my own greatness so I find it difficult to stand in front of mirrors
Infinite sword attack
You need to be careful Blackstar
If you still refuse to retreat then
Die
If you really want to kill me you're going to need a lot more than a few fancy flying swords
I'll take that
Your weapon's strength has saved you if this were a regular chain it would have broken already
This is your last warning keep your distance from here if I have to kill a kid I'll get nightmares
You bastard you're calling me a kid are you
You're wrong the kids I know are small
No stupid kid could be as big a guy as I am
Subaki transform shuriken mode
Do you know what would make you a much smaller man Mifune?
If I cut you into four of my pieces
Subaki smoke bomb mode go
Great
Yahoo
I got you now
Idiot
Why can't you learn to be quiet you blew it Blackstar
Oh no he got hit
Such a fool
No
He's not
Mifune
You're an arrogant bastard
You shouldn't use the back of the blade against an opponent who's so much bigger than you are
You know kid I'm beginning to feel real sorry for that weapon of yours
The only reason that you've survived this fight for so long is her strength and intelligence
But no matter how good a weapon may be it's wasted if an unskilled master is wielding it
You're just a useless little kid
Can't you see that?
You're wrong about him
Sure Blackstar is a little bit a little bit careless sometimes
But if he really tried I know he could do it
Mifune
It's your move
What now?
I don't have an agenda
I'm only here to protect Angela
That's not really it though is it?
I know what you're trying to do Mifune
I understand it real well
You want to beat me to make me look small
So that you'll appear greater by comparison
But I won't let you get away with that
You can look high or low but you won't find a bigger guy than me
I'm gonna win this battle
You got me?
That's interesting his eye color changed
Tsubaki switch to ninja blade mode
All right
Mifune I hope you're ready now we fight for real
Now we fight for real
I won't be using the back of the blade this time
Assassin's rule number one
Silence
Dissolve in the darkness and erase your breath
Wait for an opening to attack your target
Assassin's rule number two
Transpositional thinking
Analyze the target in order to predict his thoughts and movements
What's happening?
Is this the same brat from a minute ago?
Assassin's rule number three
Impossible
I should be able to hear his breath from here
No, wait
I can hear some faint breathing
But it can't be his
This kid can't control anything
Speed
Before the target notices your presence
Wait, I know who you are
Take the target out
We call this one the Shadow Star
What?
Finishing strike Black Star Big Wave
I am the Star
You lose
You didn't even see me coming, did you?
That's the third role of being a great assassin
So foolish
Don't blame yourself
You never had a shot at beating me
Like I said, you'd need more than some fancy flying swords
Tsubaki
Right
Where's the witch?
Huh?
Stop it!
No!
Batman, don't hurt Mifune!
No, Angela
He's my guardian
I'm a witch
But I'm still just a little kid
So Mifune is protecting me
So mister, please don't hurt my Mifune
This girl is the witch Angela?
Black Star
We have the scattered souls of the Al Capone gang
And a witch without magical power right in front of us
I don't know that we'll ever have a chance like this again
Uh...
Okay, but...
J-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j!
Get him you little brat!
Mifune!
You're free to go ahead and take my life
But...
If killing Angela is what you want, assassin
I swear on my sword, I will defend her
What should we do?
Huh?
a guardian who babysits a little witch all day please you aren't even worth the effort
let's go subaki right i mean really i can't kill a kid it would give me nightmares
are you sure about this yeah i mean it's not like i killed him myself
it's not setting the best example to say this but you should take while the taking's good
nah big guy like me doesn't need people to do his dirty work for him isn't that right subaki
assassin's rule number one silence dissolve in the darkness and erase your breath
wait for an opening to attack your target
i told you silence means approaching quietly
the future doesn't look very promising
death the kid son of lord death the grim reaper a perfect boy with nearly perfect skill and talent to match
that's the thief lupin your soul has become a quesha egg it is pure evil
and now we have come to claim it but the kid is obsessed with perfection
just look patty your stance is off again the two of you aren't in a line
i'm sorry kid and this obsession is his one great weakness prologue three death the kid
is coming soon
kuzuboshi
kizu
kuzi
k
kizu
吐く息は白いままなのに 今をぶっ壊しに行こうって約束したあの日から きっとまだ間に合うはずだから
I wanna be not so long 絶望と一緒に 悲鳴をあげ 突き刺され 全てが変わる前に
I wanna be not so long
That was big and I mean really big don't you think?
I don't know about that Black Star.You didn't recover any souls.
Clearly you're just jealous of my bigness.
That's enough about you right now.In the next episode I hear Lord Death's son is the star.
What?You're telling me Lord Death has a son?
And does that mean Lord Death is married?When did that happen?
On the next episode of Soul Eater.The perfect boy.Death the kid's magnificent mission.
Watch it or I'll take your soul.
fizer your nerve worry there.
No.
afraid of it.
hazır
どうなったら 日の活気を付け入れたぜだねというわけで
It's ok
LA的な
DER
もう couple